Guide to the Yale School of Drama Student Records for the Classes of 1927-1993
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Drama student records for the Classes of 1927-1993
RU 230
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
99.5
The records consist of student records maintained by the Yale School of Drama.
Yale School of Drama
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-F (YRG 22-F), Student records of the Yale School of Drama.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the Yale School of Drama.
Arrangement
The records for the classes of 1928-1982 are arranged alphabetically. Subsequent classes are arranged by class year.
College students; Yale School of Drama; Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Classes of 1927-1982, Accession 1986-A-026
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Wiseman, Philip R. (Box 60, Folder 4004)
- Student records for the Classes of 1983-1984, Accession 1991-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Class of 1983
  - Class of 1984
- Student records for the Classes of 1985-1986, Accession 1991-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Masters of Fine Arts, 1985
    - Registrar's office held the following pending Doctor of Fine Arts Award:
      - See year of Doctor of Fine Arts Award for:
  - Masters of Fine Arts, 1986
    - Registrar's Office held pending Doctor of Fine Arts Award:
- Student records for the Class of 1987, Accession 1993-A-008
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
- Student records for the Class of 1988, Accession 1995-A-031
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
- Student records for the Class of 1989, Accession 1996-A-010
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
- Student records for the Class of 1990, Accession 1998-A-013
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
- Student records for the Classes of 1991-1993, Accession 2004-A-171
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Class of 1991
  - Class of 1992
  - Class of 1993